Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app
Are you okay?
No.
Do I need to get the doctor?
No. no.
You can't help me.
But you just did.
Are you sure about that?
Are you kidding me?
Do you know how much joy
this has given me?
I… I mean. I can't really tell right now.
Oh no. My. uh…
My cancer's eating away at my body.
but my soul is happy.
Did you see the look on their faces?
Yeah. I did.
They looked like
they were devastated to me.
And that makes me wanna fight to live
just to see that every damn day.
I got those sons of bitches.
All of them.
Are they that bad?
You have no idea.
Kimmie's gonna be all right?
My father. there's a lot
of stipulations in his will.
Anything happens to her.
they won't get their shares.
They won't touch her.
If not. I would have been dead
a long time ago.
Okay. that's fine for me.
but what about my sister and Rain?
Don't worry.
No.
I need them protected.
and I want it in writing.
Okay. um…
My father's will. uh.
can't be touched or objected to…
but mine can be.
Okay. I'll. uh…
I'll add them to be protected.
That's… That's what I wanna do.
And Angel?
Um…
Angel is good. Yeah.
Where is he?
I actually don't know.
Well. you should find him.
Um. I wanna see him.
All right.
I'll call him.
Also. we need to talk about
you saying I'm their new boss.
Ah. did you see their faces
when I said that part?
Yeah. I did. but--
You want her to run the company?
Horace. I don't know nothing
about running a company.
It's all right. I got the right people
in place. uh. who will help you.
And who is that?
I'll fill you in.
but I… I… I need to rest now.
All right.
And. um. find Angel.
He's not answering.
We'll find him.
Find him.
Okay. you should head to the house.
The house?
Yes. Uh…
Um. James. um. my… my butler. is there.
-You have a butler?
-Yes.
He's got the place all set up.
um. for all of you.
Wait. what?
Yes.
Shit. I'm getting out of here.
There's a driver out there.
His name is. uh. Alex.
and. uh. he works for Jules.
-Oh. hell no.
-Hold on.
I've had him checked out.
He's a real cop. He just got caught up.
But yeah. he's got some. uh…
some special skills I wanna use.
Nah. I don't wanna be around nobody
that works for Jules.
Right.
No. you two listen.
It's not about who you can trust.
'cause you can't trust
none of these motherfuckers.
It's about leverage.
and we've got a lot on him.
Okay?
Now…
…the first thing I'm gonna teach you
is gonna be the hardest
for you and Angel to learn.
It's easy to play games with a nigga
who looks at what's in front of him.
but I'm gonna teach you
how to look around corners
and into the future.
Leverage is the way.
Son of a bitch.
Who is that girl?
-I don't know. You wanna tell your mother?
-Mallory. chill.
-Well. somebody better tell me something.
-Oh. what about you. Jules?
You have the pleasure.
Maybe we should go to your place
to discuss this.
I would agree.
-That's fine.
-I don't want your Black ass at my house.
-Roy--
-How the fuck did you let this happen?
Because I didn't know.
Bullshit.
-He didn't.
-You would know that. huh?
He didn't know. okay? He tried to warn me.
Well. if he didn't know.
how did he try to warn you?
I… I. uh. certainly didn't know
it was all of this.
I found out this morning
just like the rest of you.
This is some bullshit.
My wife dies. and he gets married.
Now. I wanna know who she is.
I wanna know everything about her.
And what is this shit
about her being our boss?
Yeah. that part.
She is his wife. and he can put anyone in
as CEO that he wants.
Even though she doesn't know a thing
about what that means?
Or how to spell it.
-I've seen her somewhere before.
-Where?
I don't know. but I have.
I can't believe this bullshit.
As I suggested before. maybe we should go
somewhere else to discuss this.
Rain.
Jules.
How are you?
How do I look?
Alive.
That's more than I can say for some.
Do you two know each other?
Oh. yeah.
We go way back.
So perhaps you should remember that
in your tone.
Yeah.
Okay. who is Alex?
That would be me.
Come with me.
What do you want with him? He's my driver.
Get another one.
He works for me.
And you work for Kimmie now.
Wow.
Right. Jules?
Kimmie.
Mrs. Bellarie. motherfucker.
Oh my goodness. the language.
She got more where that came from.
Are these your sons?
Unfortunately.
No. yes. they are.
Then I'm sure you've heard worse
than that shit.
I don't think we've met.
Hi. I'm Mallory.
I know who you are.
Welcome to the family.
Now I remember.
Didn't I see you shaking your ass
on a pole at Delinda's?
Didn't I see you coming out
of the bathroom
with one of the male dancers
with traces of coke on your nose.
wiping your mouth?
Oh. she quick. I might like you.
All right. bitch. I like you.
I got your bitch.
Horace wants to see you.
Who? Me?
I'm looking at you.
Go talk to the doctor. and I'll be back.
-That bitch really took my fucking driver.
-That's not all she's gonna take.
-This shit don't make no damn sense.
-I'll say.
It is…
-What's funny?
-This… This family.
Mm.
-Then why are you a part of it. Mallory?
-Go to hell.
Oh. shit. that's right. That's right.
'Cause you broke as shit.
If you didn't have me. you would--
Nigga. please. If I didn't have you. what?
-What?
-You heard me.
I heard yo ass. I'd be sitting on a yacht
with a billionaire if I didn't have you.
Hmm.
-Sitting on a yacht with a billionaire?
-I would be.
-Oh. shit. Uh-huh.
-That's what I would be doing.
-What you doing?
-You have my permission. Do that.
Why'd you take your ring off?
What the hell? I will…
You know. you underestimate
the power of a beautiful woman. Roy.
-I don't.
-That's what the hell you do.
-Not shit.
-Whatever.
You know what?
You'd be on that yacht for a day. A day.
Then he'd throw your ass overboard
before you even finished your first drink.
Look at… Look at my darn husband.
Look at you though.
This is some funny shit.
You were sleeping with a whore
that was sleeping with yo damn daddy.
Ew. What's that…
How you let Jules do that to you?
-He didn't do shit.
-How you let him do that to you?
And he did do shit. because you asked him
to set you up. and that's what he did.
He set you up. That's what he did.
-Will you shut up. Mallory?
-No. I'm not gonna shut up.
-Jules a nasty-ass bastard.
-Look at… He a nasty-ass.
He got you and Horace
running up in the same whore
that works at a strip club.
Isn't that nasty? You better tell me
every fucking thing too.
And I mean everything.
I ain't saying shit to you.
-You know I'mma find out anyway. right?
-Then do it.
-Like I always do.
Stop with the threats.
Just… Just fucking do it.
If you gonna do it. do it.
You got all these threats.
-There ain't no threat.
-All you do is threat.
But now we got this bitch…
-Then do it. Mallory.
-…coming to the company.
and I gotta see her ass every day.
-She ain't gonna do shit. She's not.
-She's gonna come to the company.
She's gonna be in your daddy's office
that's right across from mine.
I wish she would. I'd throw
her ass out the fucking window.
-Oh. like she did yo ass?
-Damn right.
If you throw her out the window.
then all our shares are gone.
You know whose fault this really is?
It's that big musclehead-ass nigga.
-That's whose fault it is.
-Ain't no big musclehead. It's your daddy.
It's Horace.
He did this because your ass taunted him.
It ain't my fault.
-It is your fault.
-Shit.
When your ass was laying
in that hospital bed taunting him.
I told you he would do this.
-Are you through?
-I'm not.
I'm actually not at all.
'cause I bet your ass a million dollars
that he's gonna make sure
you and Charles are out that damn will.
-He can't do that.
-He can. You didn't think he'd do this.
-I wish that nigga would die.
-Don't… Don't say that.
You don't want that.
-Yes. I do.
-No. you don't.
Because then we'll be stuck with that
whore Kimmie running the damn company.
And trust me. you don't want that.
I can't believe this shit.
Thank you.
Um…
I'm gonna go check on Rain and my sister.
No. no. Hold on.
Attorney Varney. I need you to add
Sylvie. Rain. and Angel to my will
as part of our family.
Yes. sir.
So they can be protected from the others.
Yes. sir. Will do.
And I need it tight.
I'll use the same language
your father used. sir.
-It'll be airtight.
-Good.
When can you do it?
I can get on it
as soon as I leave here. sir.
Okay. I need it done today.
Absolutely.
I want you to tell her everything.
Wait.
How do I know
if he's gonna tell me everything?
You can leave.
Yes. sir.
Kimmie. I told you not to ask me questions
like that in front of other people.
You can't trust
none of these motherfuckers.
Now. I'm gonna be in yo ass.
You got a lot to learn before I die.
I'm not gonna be here that long.
And I don't have time to worry about
hurting your feelings. You got me?
Yeah.
Yes.
Now. what he doesn't know
is that I've got another firm.
Everything that he tells me.
I have three lawyers verify it.
Let him tell you everything.
Pay attention. Record it if you have to.
Then you go to the firm
and you ask them questions.
You play 'em against each other.
Okay. Got it.
They don't like him because he's so smart.
but you verify everything.
Got it.
Did you find Angel yet?
No. not yet.
Okay. you should…
You should go to the house.
I have one more issue.
What?
That night when Jules was chasing me.
I stole a car.
There was a man in the back seat.
and he's the father-in-law
of someone named Daniel Lakeland.
How do you know that?
Angel saw it on the news.
That's why I have on this hat and coat.
Where's the car now?
It was in the parking garage last I knew.
What?
Angel went to go check on it.
All right. y-y-you. uh…
You head to the house.
and… and. uh. I'll… I'll handle it.
Okay.
Thank you.
Call Charles.
What?
Are you there?
Mm. am I where?
At your brother's house. Charles.
-I ain't going over there.
-Charles.
Look. I need to get some rest.
I'm going to the club tonight.
Are you taking this seriously?
Well. shit. he married her.
What can I do? It's done.
Charles. you need
to be thinking about this.
I don't need to think about shit but
where my next piece of ass is coming from.
I also think I want Chinese tonight.
Charles…
Look. Varney.
you told me.
You tried to warn me.
Why did you tell them that?
Well. you did.
Yeah. but I told you in confidence.
Well…
Charles. you can't tell them
the shit that I'm telling you.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Maybe I just won't tell you shit.
That would be great.
-Charles…
-Look. I gotta go.
Charles. are you going over there or what?
Look. I got another call
on the other line.
You don't have anybody
on the other line. Charles.
It's not a telephone line.
it's a line of coke.
Okay.
Bye. Varney.
Bye.
Well. you're doing better.
So we can discharge you.
-That's it? That's all I need?
-Well. we'll need to do a follow-up.
-Okay. I'll come back.
-Stay on the blood thinners.
-and if you have any pain…
-I'll come back to see you.
Okay. good.
Oh. did I come with any clothes?
Uh. no. actually. But I'll have the nurse
bring you something to wear home.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Sure.
Hey.
Home?
I can't wait to see what that looks like.
-Yeah. it looks crazy online.
-Let me see.
You see the horses?
-That's nothing.
-Wow.
Wait till y'all see it in person.
-Well. shit. let's go. I'm ready.
-Wait. wait. wait. wait. wait.
How do you feel about
this driver situation?
The Alex dude?
Look. we in this shit now.
He said to trust the man. so we just gotta
see what he's talking about.
I don't know. Rain.
Kimmie. the man just married you
without a prenup.
If this is even all legit.
It is.
Things are finally going good for us.
Can we just go with it?
I'll go with it when he makes sure
you two are straight.
He will.
You say he will like you know him. Rain.
You do not know this man.
Kimmie. I know we gotta trust somebody.
Shit. I'm ready to do this.
This man got a mansion and horses
we can ride without getting paid.
Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
Hey. nurse. where my clothes at?
This place is far out.
Yeah. but it's worth it.
Why you say that?
Well. when you see it. you'll know why.
So how long have you worked for Jules?
I'm a cop for the city of Chicago. ma'am.
-Should I ask him again?
-Yeah. you should.
How long have you worked for Jules?
I don't work for Jules.
I work for the Bellarie family.
Okay. so he on that shit.
What?
Nothing.
-Why are you speaking to him like that?
-'Cause this nigga don't wanna talk.
He's Japanese.
He's a nigga.
Only niggas work for Jules.
What is your racial background?
I'm Japanese.
Nah. you got some soul in there somewhere.
I'm Black and Dutch.
See? Nigga.
Japanigga.
You do know I know who you are. right?
You mean besides my name?
I was at Delinda's. hiding behind a couch
the night that you
and the other so-called cop
came in there
looking for somethin' for Jules.
I heard y'all talking.
Well. if you remember correctly.
I was telling Officer Trackson
that everything you'd been through.
I don't blame you for what you did.
What did she do?
She broke a very expensive table.
young lady.
You know. I think you're gonna
really love the house.
They live a really lavish lifestyle.
Save all the small talk.
We keeping an eye on you.
I'm glad you are.
We don't like or trust you.
I can understand that.
One wrong move…
Yeah.
I got it.
And who been running the club
now that Delinda's…
table is broke?
There's a lot of broken furniture here.
Nobody really.
We were there last night
trying to hold it all together.
Hm.
"Hm" what?
-Nothing.
-Nah. what?
I know you.
I know you do.
So this table can't be repaired?
Not a chance.
What about Body?
Body's in the hospital.
She in the hospital?
Yeah.
She's alive?
Yeah. from what I heard.
Hm.
I guess her table didn't break as bad.
More broken ta-- What are y'all doing?
Where these tables come from. IKEA?
Well. I guess we gonna have to pay
somebody a little visit.
No. we don't.
We ain't visiting nobody. Rain.
Kimmie. you got unfinished business
with her. and I do too.
And I'll handle it.
No. you already done broke a table.
Can I at least break a chair?
What the hell are y'all talking about?
Amazon orders. girl. Be quiet.
You know Daga?
Daga? No.
They call her the Pump Queen.
No. I don't. but I can find her.
Yeah. you do that.
I need to have a word with both of them.
All right. I'm on it.
Where the hell are they?
Left before I did.
Call them.
I did.
Why the hell are we meeting here anyway?
Because we need to figure this shit out.
What we need to figure out
is how to take his ass down.
Oh. Norman.
Oh. wait a minute.
Didn't you try to rob him?
-Are you still on that?
-Huh?
You know damn well he don't carry
that much money at that safe house.
-Just get out of my face.
-Are you broke?
Hell no.
You are broke. aren't you?
You never did keep your money very well.
Are you gambling again?
Is this a conversation
you want to have with me?
-This is a conversation we having.
-I am not broke.
Wait. so you are over-leveraged.
and you need that money every month.
Are you done?
Come on. you can tell me.
You know what? Maybe if I ran
an illegal operation out of a strip club.
I'd have extra cash too. just like you.
Okay. okay. this is about greed then.
You know the last motherfucker
who said that to me had to get in the bag.
You still doing that old-school shit
I taught you?
Do you want me to get a bag for you?
How much money do you need?
All of it. you greedy motherfucker.
Just like you want it all.
and you will stop at nothing to get it.
Baby. we both in the will.
Well. then you know
exactly why we're here.
-Here comes the colon sculpture.
-Shut up.
-Are they not here?
-They're on their way.
Shit. I'm going back home.
Wait a minute. Here they come.
What… Where the hell is Attorney Varney?
We'll talk about it inside. Mom.
Oh. there you are.
-You're nasty.
-Shut up.
Excuse me. He wanted to see me.
About what?
Well. he wanted to add
some people to the will.
-What?
-He wanted to protect them from you all.
Well. you better make sure
that shit is airtight for us.
You need to ask the right questions.
And what are the questions. dear? Hm?
Why the fuck he protecting them?
The question is.
who are the people. Varney?
Well. the people you saw in the room.
and someone named Angel.
-Who? Angel?
-Yeah.
-Hm.
-He didn't have his last name for him.
-Okay. that's odd.
-But he's gonna get it for me later.
And what does this Angel look like?
I have no idea.
Hm.
What is it. little brother?
Is that name turning you on?
Well. the Angel I know does some--
Look. look. I do not wanna hear
no disgusting shit right now.
He works at the club with Kimmie.
-What?
-Yeah.
Well. what kind of club is this?
-I could take you there.
-Will you just stop it?
This is serious.
I am too. I'm going tonight.
We don't wanna hear this shit.
You old nigga.
Do your ears even work? Shut up.
Look. you little motherfucker. I'll come
over there and whoop your mother--
-Norman. please.
-Whoa. hey. hey. hey. hey. Calm down.
-Calm down.
-Lord. have mercy.
I cannot believe that he married
some whore just to get even.
No. he did it to get ahead.
Well. then we all know that it isn't love.
so surely we can challenge it.
-You know. that's what we should do.
-Let's hear what the attorney has to say.
Mallory. don't talk to me
like I'm fucking stupid.
Well. I don't want the attorney.
Varney. in here.
-You just shut the fuck up.
-He's a damn quack. Mom.
Listen. can we contest it?
Have… Have the man committed
and say he's incompetent.
That's exactly what we should do.
He don't even know this bitch.
Attorney Varney.
Well. that's why he wanted
the witnesses there…
and a judge to do a cognitive test
to prove that he's in his right mind.
Obviously. he's not in his right mind
if he doing this stupid-ass shit
with that bitch.
Okay. so there's nothing
that we can do legally?
I'm afraid not.
He protected his shares
and diluted some of yours.
This son of a bitch.
How much?
Well. him being the eldest son.
he exercised his 10%.
Well. it's not as bad
as I thought.
From each of you.
Each of us?
-Shit.
-I'm afraid so.
-What?
-10% for me is…
Do you know how much money I'll be losing?
No. that's all of us.
This motherfucker.
This shit is not over with.
Who is this bitch?
I wanna know everything about her.
This is only the beginning.
You know what?
I'm not standing for this.
Hell no. I am not doing it.
Okay. well. um…
I guess you'll explain to me
how this messes with my money.
-I'll get you those numbers later.
-Great.
Ooh. can you make it soon. please?
'Cause I'm going out tonight.
So… Excuse me.
Thank you.
Are you a fucking mannequin. nigga?
Why you still standing there?
Go ruin someone else's life. man.
That'll be all. Attorney Varney.
Thank you.
Just give me a call
if you learn anything else.
Will do.
No. no. no. no. no. no. no. no.
Don't call her. nigga. Call me.
Excuse me?
Did you not hear me. nigga?
Don't ever call my wife again.
Now bounce. bro.
Bounce. What…
-Why are you such an asshole?
-Damn.
Hm. Let me ask you something.
Did you know that big nigga
was fucking my wife?
-What?
-Yeah.
Why don't we just
all hop on this lie train?
-I'm not telling no lie.
-You are a liar.
But why don't we get to the truth?
The truth is. like I told you in the car.
the motherfucking bitch
that you were sleeping with
is now married to your father!
Isn't this some sick shit?
You and your daddy
fucking the same piece of pussy.
Let me talk to you.
-Sure.
-Uh. um…
-In my office?
-Garage.
No. you don't. Not in private.
-Mallory. what--
-What did I say?
You better be careful.
Your mother's not here.
What the fuck that supposed to mean?
And what is that.
your… your resting bitch face?
No.
This is my "I'm looking
at a stupid motherfucker" face.
-I'm stupid?
-You stupid motherfucker.
I wanna know everything about this bitch.
-And I mean every damn thing.
-Wha… What are you. the president?
No. I'm the fixer.
and I fix all your shit.
I fix your father's shit.
I fix your mother's shit.
the company shit.
So I am the shit.
Are you done?
Yeah. I am. I'm done with you. Years ago.
But. Jules.
there is one thing I couldn't fix.
How's your erectile dysfunction going?
It works perfectly. with another woman.
-Like I said. let's talk.
-No. the fuck--
-I'mma follow right behind your ass.
-Mallory. let me talk to him.
But you know what. Jules?
Do you know how disappointing it is
to have a man with a dick that curves?
-You should--
-I don't know anything about that.
Let me just talk to him for a second.
-No.
-Let… Let me just-- Please. please.
-Let me--
-Fine. Fuck it. Talk.
Jules. Jules. Jules.
-I know. I know. I know.
-No. no. no. no. no. no. no.
No. no. you don't know.
-Did you set him up?
-What did I tell you?
I don't give a damn what you told me.
Did you put that bitch in his bed?
Why would I do that?
Yeah. you did it. Mm-hmm.
Just think about it. I wouldn't do that.
No. no. you would do some shit like that.
That's the thing. you would.
Roy. you need to calm down. all right?
I can always get you another girl.
That's the thing.
I don't trust you no more.
Matter of fact.
I've been working on one for you.
You gonna love her.
Submissive. do anything you want.
You said that about the last girl.
and look at the situation we in right now.
Yeah. I know. but this one
is a for sure. for sure. I'm telling you.
Yeah. if you say so.
Come on. You know me.
I do know you. Jules. I do.
And like I said. look at
the fucking situation we in right now.
She literally lives
with my fucking father.
Let me just set it up.
Go to the hotel.
You gonna love her.
Just give me a couple of days.
A couple of days. huh?
Roy.
Roy. you need to calm down.
I know you got a lot going on.
I do.
So do what you need to do.
and get in the hotel and just do your job.
Okay?
Done.
And another thing.
that nigga that was driving
my wife around. the tall one…
-Yeah. what about him?
-I don't wanna see him again.
Okay. he's gone.
And I mean it.
Okay.
I gotta go.
Okay. I got it.
Sheesh.
-Is she still in there?
-Mm-hmm.
Fucking junkies.
What's up. Trackson?
Yo. yo. what the hell?
What did y'all get him on?
He was in the stolen car
that Lakeland was in.
-What?
-Oh yeah.
You got yourself in some deep shit. boy.
Tell me about it.
Yeah.
Jules.
You won't believe this.
I don't got time for small talk.
Angel is here.
Where is he?
He's here at the police station.
They arrested him
for the Lakeland carjacking.
You keep him right there. I'm on my way.
I'll be here. I got him.
♪ You feel that? ♪
♪ Aye. sweet on my nigga
Tell him thank you for the hit ♪
♪ And what? ♪
♪ Breaking up. nigga
We ain't breaking this ♪
♪ Come try your luck
If you bust ♪
♪ When we finish
We gonna touch. after that… ♪
Hello.
Hi. May I speak to Felicia?
Who this is?
Mallory.
Who?
The lady on the perm box.
Oh. shit. Hey.
Hi.
What's up?
I have $1.000 for you.
Well. shit. you need to bring that to me.
Look. you haven't
called me about Kimmie.
Oh. 'Cause I ain't seen her.
Oh. no?
Well. actually. I did see her.
But look. you gonna have to tell me
what you want all this information for.
-Listen. do you want the money?
-Hell yeah.
Yeah. okay. then tell me.
Mm. I don't talk without cash.
Most whores don't.
Excuse me?
Just give me that money.
I'll meet you with it.
Nah. I ain't that stupid.
Actually. I think you are.
-What?
-Do you want the money or not?
Hell yeah. In my damn hand.
How about we do this?
Why don't you tell me a little something.
then I'll come meet you with the money
and then you can tell me the rest?
Now. why would I do that?
Felicia. it's business.
It's like a deposit.
Depo-- Do you know
how much money I make at the club?
I also know that your throat is sore
when you do.
and you need a trip to the clinic.
Clinic?
You know what? You a real bitch.
No. I am.
And I'm offering you the kind of money
to where you don't have to run
to the clinic after.
Man. I ain't fucking with you.
Will you fuck with $3.000?
I wouldn't care if it was $10.000.
If I ain't got that money in my hand.
baby. I ain't telling you shit.
How about this?
What's your address?
I can come and get it from you.
I'm not giving you my address.
You not coming here.
Well. then. get off my phone.
Listen. I--
♪ Thank you for the hit ♪
♪ Breaking up. nigga
You ain't breaking this ♪
♪ Come try your luck if you-- ♪
Did this girl hang up?
Siri. redial her 10.000 times.
Ah.
What up?
What a day.
You ain't gonna pour me one?
Do you know what I love?
What? Me?
How you just be walking in here
like this yo house.
Well. it ain't gonna be yours either
if you don't start taking this seriously.
And what does that mean?
Charles. you got diluted by 10%.
Um. about $8 million.
Well. okay.
Do you know what that means?
Mm. you just told me.
Charles. do you even look at the accounts?
Let me explain this to you.
as I have over and over again.
You get a certain amount of money
each month based on your shares.
If that goes down. as it has.
you're not going to be able
to afford this house.
or your cars.
or your whores.
or your drugs.
Okay. well. make sure
that shit don't happen. Shit.
And again.
you not taking this seriously.
You know all them numbers and shit
give me a headache. I don't know.
Okay. good.
Why should I care if you don't?
You better care.
Why should I if you don't?
Varney. I appreciate
you looking out for me.
Okay? But…
But what?
Hm?
Aren't you worried
about your car being parked out front?
No.
I told them I was coming over here
to talk to you. And it's in your garage.
The fuck you park in my garage for?
Why not?
You got an empty space
'cause of the Lambo. right?
Oh yeah. You remember that night.
Chasing your whores. car gets shot up.
We think you're dead.
You know. all that shit.
All that bullshit you keep
putting us through. Remember that?
That's why it's in the garage.
All right. so I guess
your little excuse worked. huh?
It's not an excuse.
Hm.
I came over here to talk to you. Again.
If you say so.
Where you going?
Take a nap.
How the hell am I supposed
to help you help yourself?
Well…
you know how horny I get.
I'm talking about with money. Charles.
That's not what I need right now.
You do know your dad is in the hospital?
And he's dying.
You know that. right?
Yeah.
But all you can think about is sex.
And I'll be thinking about sex
at his funeral.
Do you wanna fuck or not?
I really… I really don't
understand you.
I bet you understand this ass.
Well. if you wanna fuck.
I'll be in the bedroom. If not. leave.
Hey. your dad is dying.
You know that. right?
So all you think about is sex?
Shit.
Why my dumb ass
keep falling for this shit?
Wow. This is his house?
Why they just
standing there like that?
-Like a scary movie kind of.
-Right?
Secure.
Welcome.
Damn.
What?
I just--
I just never seen it in the daytime.
I know.
What kind of fairy tale shit is this?
I told you it was special.
Hello. Mrs. Bellarie.
Oh.
Hello. Hi.
Are you James?
Yes. I'm James. James the butler. ma'am.
I'm told that you have no bags.
No. we don't.
Well. Mr. Bellarie wanted me to assure
that you have all that you need.
Let me introduce you to your staff.
Lydia. she's your chef.
John is your sous chef.
Margaret is the head of housekeeping.
And this is Glen. He and his team
take care of the grounds and the stables.
-Shh. chill.
-Oh. what's that old shack doing up there?
Look kind of out of place.
Well. that's actually the house
that Mr. Bellarie's father grew up in.
His great-grandfather
bought all this land.
Quite a feat for a former slave.
wouldn't you say?
And all the family's mansions
are built on this property.
All the mansions that we just passed?
Yes.
That's all the family's?
Yes. ma'am.
Wait. so Roy lives on this road?
He's the first house
that you pass on the right.
He and his lovely wife Mallory live there.
Mallory?
What's she like?
She is delightful. You will love her.
She already does.
Rain.
You do.
And this is Whitman.
He's the head of security.
They don't talk?
Girl. shut up.
-This is incredible.
-They just standing there.
Let's get you all inside.
I'll be here if you need anything.
Okay. they're heading inside.
So how is she?
I don't know yet.
-You'll be appointed to her team?
-Yeah.
Okay. Well. come on.
I'll show you the ropes
and where you'll be staying.
All right. let's go.
You got any military experience?
Mm. you are something else.
Yeah.
You know you need to get
some curtains for this house. right?
There's not another house
that can see in here.
Okay.
You big old freak.
I'm just a freak for you.
So. what was this all about?
What do you mean?
You come in here seducing me.
You up to somethin'.
Huh.
If I ain't mistaken.
you seduced me just now.
Mm.
So. what's up? Tell me.
You don't get it.
You still don't get it. do you?
No. I get it.
-Get it?
-Mm-hmm.
What is it that you get?
Tell me.
You don't want me to go out.
Nigga. I never want you to go out.
What is it you wanna tell me? Hm?
That I love you.
Oh. that. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Charles. come on.
What do you mean…
"Oh. that"?
Huh?
Look. that's not gonna keep me
from going out tonight. so…
Hm.
Um…
Will I ever be enough for you?
No.
Bitch.
What do you mean. "no"?
Look. I wanna get some rest.
Why?
'Cause I put it on you. right?
I wanna get some rest
so I can be up all night.
What? Get off me.
Fuck you.
Fuck you. dude.
-Fuck you.
-Varney. Varney.
-Shit.
-Varney.
What?
You just did.
I mean. but not good enough
for me to stay.
Oh. Charles. you know what?
You're a piece of shit.
Why do I fuck with you?
Because I got you
wrapped around my finger.
Yeah. you keep believing this shit.
I do. It's true.
You better be glad I need some rest.
Let you fuck me again. bwoy.
You'll be back. Varney.
See you later. Varney.
You wanna fuck me. Varney.
What the fuck did I just hear?
♪ Walkin' through the city streets ♪
♪ Neon lights. crowded seats ♪
♪ Every face has a story to tell ♪
♪ There's people that I gotta meet ♪
♪ Places that I gotta be ♪
♪ When I saw you
I just tripped and fell ♪
♪ But I'm searching for
A different kind of thrill ♪
♪ Like living on a hill ♪
♪ Counting hundred dollar bills ♪
♪ What I'm searching for's
A different kind of thrill ♪
♪ Not like poppin' pills
Like a million dollar bills ♪
♪ Let's escape the noise
I'm not like them other boys ♪
♪ I see that darkness in your eye
But I'm not paranoid ♪
♪ I could fulfill your needs ♪
♪ She said. "Don't lie to me" ♪
♪ Then we enter the void
Every day is Halloween ♪
♪ Now wait a minute
Ooh. I'm back up in it ♪
♪ Ooh. I'm back up in it ♪
♪ Ooh. I'm back up in it. yeah ♪
♪ Now wait a minute
Ooh. I'm back up in it ♪
♪ Ooh. I'm back up in it ♪
♪ Ooh. I'm back up in it. yeah ♪
♪ Walking through the city streets ♪
♪ Neon lights. crowded seats ♪
♪ Every face has a story to tell ♪
♪ There's people that I gotta meet ♪
♪ Places that I gotta be ♪
♪ When I saw you
I just tripped and fell ♪
♪ But I'm searching for
A different kind of thrill ♪
♪ Like living on a hill ♪
♪ Counting hundred dollar bills ♪
♪ What I'm searching for's
A different kind of thrill ♪
♪ Not like poppin' pills
Like a million dollar bills ♪
♪ Walking through the city streets ♪
♪ Neon lights. crowded seats ♪
♪ Every face has a story to tell ♪
♪ There's people that I gotta meet ♪
♪ Places that I gotta be ♪
♪ When I saw you
I just tripped and fell ♪
♪ But I'm searching for
A different kind of thrill ♪
♪ Like living on a hill ♪
♪ Counting hundred dollar bills ♪
♪ What I'm searching for's
A different kind of thrill ♪
♪ Not like poppin' pills ♪
♪ Like a million dollar bills ♪
Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app